{
    "introduction": {
        "script" : ["Welcome to the world of Endowus. This game is a simulation in which you will be able to test out different portfolios in mock scenarios, this will allow you to find the portfolio that you are the most comfortable with.", "We all have different risk appetites or risk tolerance. If you invest in a way that is not compatible with the amount of volatility or short-term loss you are comfortable taking, you are setting up for failure when the markets inevitably move against you as you may make investment decisions that go against your long-term financial well-being. ", "As it is a simulation, feel free to restart by refreshing the browser to test out another portfolio!"],
        "externalURL" : "https://endowus.com/support/360007646114-why-do-i-need-to-choose-my-risk-tolerance-and-how-is-it-understood"
    },

    "equities100": {
        "description": "100% Equities",
        "script": ["A very aggressive portfolio designed for longer term goals that can withstand periods of significant volatility to compound returns over the long term and achieve higher average expected returns.", "This portfolio has a High Risk Tolerance of 50%. This means that this portfolio may lose up to 50% in the worst case scenarios, based on historical 12-month percentage loss."],
        "annualisedReturn": 12.18,
        "volatility": 11.03,
        "riskTolerance": 50,
        "externalURL": "https://endowus.com/flagship"
    },
    "equities80": {
        "description": "80% Equities\n20% Fixed Income",
        "script": ["An aggressive portfolio designed for longer term goals that can withstand periods of volatility to compound returns over the long term and achieve higher average expected returns.", "This portfolio has a High Risk Tolerance of 40%. This means that this portfolio may lose up to 40% in the worst case scenarios, based on historical 12-month percentage loss."],
        "annualisedReturn": 10.77,
        "volatility": 9.27,
        "riskTolerance": 40,
        "externalURL": "https://endowus.com/flagship"
    },
    "equities60": {
        "description": "60% Equities\n40% Fixed Income",
        "script": ["A balanced portfolio designed for mid to long term goals and cashflows that can withstand periods of some volatility to compound returns over the long term and achieve higher average risk-adjusted returns.", "This portfolio has a Medium Risk Tolerance of 35%. This means that this portfolio may lose up to 35% in the worst case scenarios, based on historical 12-month percentage loss."],
        "annualisedReturn": 9.31,
        "volatility": 7.56,
        "riskTolerance": 35,
        "externalURL": "https://endowus.com/flagship"
    },
    "equities40": {
        "description": "40% Equities\n60% Fixed Income",
        "script": ["A measured portfolio designed for mid term to long term goals and cashflows that can withstand periods of some volatility to compound returns over the long term to achieve higher average risk-adjusted returns.", "This portfolio has a Medium Risk Tolerance of 30%. This means that this portfolio may lose up to 30% in the worst case scenarios, based on historical 12-month percentage loss."],
        "annualisedReturn": 7.78,
        "volatility": 5.89,
        "riskTolerance": 30,
        "externalURL": "https://endowus.com/flagship"
    },
    "equities20": {
        "description": "20% Equities\n80% Fixed Income",
        "script": ["A conservative portfolio designed for mid term goals and cashflows that are focused on capital preservation with recognition that a small allocation to equities can improve asset class diversification and long term risk-adjusted returns.", "This portfolio has a Low Risk Tolerance of 25%. This means that this portfolio may lose up to 25% in the worst case scenarios, based on historical 12-month percentage loss."],
        "annualisedReturn": 6.26,
        "volatility": 4.58,
        "riskTolerance": 25,
        "externalURL": "https://endowus.com/flagship"
    },
    "equities0": {
        "description": "100% Fixed Income",
        "script": ["A very conservative portfolio designed for short to mid term goals focused on capital preservation and lower volatility in returns, with some long term capital appreciation to compound returns.", "This portfolio has a Low Risk Tolerance of 12%. This means that this portfolio may lose up to 12% in the worst case scenarios, based on historical 12-month percentage loss."],
        "annualisedReturn": 4.72,
        "volatility": 3.87,
        "riskTolerance": 12,
        "externalURL": "https://endowus.com/flagship"
    },
    
    "event1": {
        "script": ["Congratulations, you have been accepted for an exchange semester at Busan University in South Korea."],
        "question": "You are required to make a payment of $8,000. How would you like to make your payment?",
        "response": "Payment for your exchange has been made!",
        "amount": -8000
    },
    "event2": {
        "script": ["You have been offered a 6-month internship at MBB & Co. Enjoy your time here & learn from your supervisors."],
        "question": "You have been paid a total of $6,000 over 6 months! How would you like to distribute your salary?",
        "amount": 6000,
        "response": "You have distributed your salary!"
    },
    "event3": {
        "script": ["Congratulations on landing your first job at ShopForward! You are ready for more responsibilities! "],
        "question": "You have earned $100,000 over 2 years of working at ShopForward! How would you like to distribute your salary?",
        "amount": 100000,
        "response": "You have distributed your salary!"
    },
    "event4": {
        "script": ["You've been promoted! Your talent and grit have earned the praise of your boss and colleagues. Enjoy your raise!"],
        "question": "Your pay has increased to $150,000 over the next 2 years of work! How would you like to distribute your salary?",
        "amount": 150000,
        "response": "You have distributed your salary!"
    },
    "event5": {
        "script": ["Your new home is now ready! Collect your keys to your brand new home."],
        "question": "The downpayment for your new home costs $30,000. How would you like to make your downpayment?",
        "amount": -30000,
        "response": "Payment for your house has been made!"
    },
    "event6": {
        "script": ["Congratulations on your marriage! Wedding bells are ringing and signalling the beginning of a new journey. Wishing you both everlasting happiness!"],
        "question": "The wedding expenses adds up to $40,000. How would you like to make your payment?",
        "amount": -40000,
        "response": "Payment for your wedding has been made!"
    },
    "event7": {
        "script": ["BINGO! You have tried your luck and won 1st prize in the latest lottery draw"],
        "question": "Your earnings for the lottery amounts to $2,000!",
        "amount": 2000,
        "response": "You have distributed the earnings"
    },
    "event8": {
        "script": ["Oh no! It's been a few years and your home decor is now outdated. Time for a renovation, imagine the new vibe of the room!"],
        "question": "The renovation works amounts to $5,000. How would you like to make your payment?",
        "amount": -5000,
        "response": "Payment for the renovation has been made!"
    },
    "event9": {
        "script": ["You have been recognised for your efforts at work! This is the company's 25th anniversary bonus & you are getting a chunk for your years of loyalty and hard work!"],
        "question": "Your bonus amounts to $100,000. How would you like to distribute it?",
        "amount": 100000,
        "response": "You have distributed your bonus!"
    },
    "event10": {
        "script": ["Your children are all grown up! What a journey, they grew up so fast. Its time for the last leg of their education journey before going out to the real world."],
        "question": "Your children's university fees amounts to about $50,000. How would you like to make your payment?",
        "amount": -50000,
        "response": "Payment for your children's university fees has been made!"
    },
    "event11": {
        "script": ["Property market is red hot! Now is the time to take profits from your larger home and downsize to a smaller apartment."],
        "question": "Your profits from downsizing amounts to $300,000. How would you like to distribute your earnings?",
        "amount": 300000,
        "response": "You have distributed your earnings!"
    },
    "event12": {
        "script": ["Your children are adults now, and are giving back to you for having raised them so well."],
        "question": "Your children provided you with $48,000. How would you like to distribute this allowance?",
        "amount": 48000,
        "response": "You have distributed your allowance!"
    },
    "event13": {
        "script": ["Oh no, the world has been hit by a drought! The semiconductor industry is now facing a shortage affecting tech stocks worldwide. Your Endowus portfolio has dipped!"],
        "question": "Would you like to withdraw your funds from your Endowus wallet? Please keep in mind that doing so will affect your overall returns.",
        "isVolatilityEvent": true
    },
    "event14": {
        "script": ["The drought is over! The semiconductor industry has gotten back on its feet and is looking as strong as ever. Your Endowus portfolio has recovered!"],
        "isVolatilityEvent": true
    },
    "event15": {
        "script": ["Congratulations! You've been promoted to Department Chief at work! Your talent and grit have earned high praises from your boss and colleagues. Enjoy your raise!"],
        "question": "Your pay has increased to a sum of $250,000 over the next 2 years of work! How would you like to distribute your salary?",
        "amount": 250000,
        "response": "You have distributed your salary!"
    },
    "event16": {
        "script": ["Your new home is now ready! Collect your keys and start a new journey with your family."],
        "question": "The inital cost of your new home is $70,000. How would you like to make your payment?",
        "amount": -70000,
        "response": "Payment for your house has been made!"
    }
}